[tense music playing]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
-[Gu-cheon pants]
-Gu-cheon.
Are you all right?
There was a reason why the Crown Prince
had lured the plague spirits right to us.
A great calamity
is about to befall the entire palace.
-[Queen breathes shakily]
-[music fades]
-[unsettling music playing]
-[murmuring]
[man 1] I apologize.
Your Majesty. that seat belongs to…
[unsettling music intensifies]
[Queen] As you well know.
His Majesty's life
currently stands in grave peril.
Your Majesty. that is just not true.
I know that the spirit still wishes
to kill the King.
I arrived here already knowing that.
Chief Royal Secretary.
There is no one else but me who can
take his place on this empty throne.
I am the only one.
It is only I
who can save the abundance altar
and the Jongmyo Shrine!
I will save it all!
-Mark my every word!
-[staff slams]
I alone
will protect it all.
-I alone will protect it all.
-[staff slams]
I must…
[music swells]
-[man 2] Left State Councillor.
-Councillor.
-[Queen gasping]
-[man 2] Councillor!
-[man 3] Councillor.
-[man 2] What is happening to him?
Left State Councillor.
[gasps. groans]
[spectral scream]
-[women screaming]
-[tense music playing]
[blade rasps]
[screaming continues]
[tense music swells]
[spectral screams]
[spectral whispering]
THE EAST PALACE
[Saeng-gang muffled] Do you believe
what happened in the palace
is tied to the Crown Prince?
Gu-cheon?
[clearly] Gu-cheon.
[Gu-cheon breathes deeply]
Sorry. what did you just say?
That the palace feels off right now.
You don't look any better either.
[Gu-cheon sighs]
It's because the Crown Prince
has grown stronger.
That is why I must seal him in here.
Seal him?
Without sending him to the afterlife?
That will be impossible to do now.
Once the plague spirits' souls
are devoured. they'll be entangled.
Oh. for heaven's sake.
Don't look at me
as though I'm about to die.
You should stop frowning.
It makes you look ugly.
You haven't looked yourself
since you acquired the gwi-mae's eyes.
Just like the well gwi-mae.
you will become--
Are you afraid that if I do this.
I'll lose my mind
and kill someone out there?
That will not happen.
[gentle music playing]
Sealing is a more useful method.
making it simpler to destroy them.
All I have to do is seal him in here.
And that will work?
The appeasement rite will be very helpful.
If we soothe
the souls of the plague spirits.
we can weaken the Crown Prince's powers.
I will walk you back to your quarters.
Let us go together.
No need to. Do I look ill to you?
Yes. because you are.
[door opens]
[gentle music continues]
It all comes down to this.
By tonight. this will all end.
That's right.
Whether it becomes porridge or rice.
What will you do when this is over
and you leave the palace?
[Gu-cheon] Hmm…
Get dead drunk. I suppose.
-And sleep for three or four days.
-[chuckles]
[Saeng-gang] No. I didn't mean like that.
How do you wanna live?
What do you wanna do with your life?
I've never thought about it.
But I will return to the temple.
[Saeng-gang chuckles] Really?
You said you hated the head monk there.
and yet you wanna go back?
The thing is. about 2.000 yards
to the southeast of the temple.
there's a river
that runs along a sheer cliff.
Right near there…
is where my mother died.
So even in death.
I cannot leave the temple.
I truly am sorry.
[music fades]
In order to solve this case. I. uh…
-I pulled someone in who didn't--
-You're only now beating that drum?
After using me?
[Saeng-gang scoffs]
You have such a talent for telling someone
the meanest. most hurtful things.
And after working up the courage
to be honest with you…
[unsettling music playing]
[distorted spectral voice]
Tonight. it will be you who dies.
The one who failed to die with his mother.
The one who should not be allowed to live.
The one who is neither man nor spirit.
Tonight. it will be you who dies.
[distorted] Tonight.
it will be you who dies.
The one who must die alongside his mother
will be the one to die tonight.
What did the emaciated gwi-mae just say?
[shaman] ♪ Turtle. turtle ♪
♪ Poke your head out ♪
♪ If you do not ♪
♪ I will roast you and eat you up ♪
[Saeng-gang] Is it almost done?
The ritual will begin
at the Hour of the Ox.
[Gu-cheon] It's nearly ready.
[clatter. scraping]
I have been thinking.
I shall go with you
to that realm to help you.
[gentle music playing]
Have I not constantly told you
that if you go in there. you will die?
Don't even consider it.
[Gu-cheon blows air]
[Gu-cheon sighs] It's all set.
I'll get going now.
Wait a moment.
Drink this
so your yang energy is replenished.
The ingredients are valuable.
Good heavens.
You didn't have to do this now.
You should've given it to me sooner.
Ugh. This medicine is so bitter. [coughs]
Is there anything I can do to help?
I'm sorry. no.
Princess.
The Crown Prince is after you as well.
Don't forget that.
So keep yourself hidden away.
[music fades]
What is wrong?
Earlier today.
I may have gone to see my grandmother.
Why did you go there?
You made her seem like your enemy.
[ominous music playing]
It will take half a day for you
to wake up after this.
[Gu-cheon breathes shakily]
[labored breathing] Why?
-Why?
-I don't know. I honestly don't.
The moment I heard the gwi-mae mention
that you would meet your end.
my body moved before I was able to stop.
[Gu-cheon breathing shakily]
[panting]
You are the only one in this palace
I can trust and rely on. That is why…
I will make sure
you don't meet your end tonight.
[labored breathing]
[Saeng-gang] I will save you.
even if that means
sacrificing my own life for yours.
[music intensifies]
Thank you for always protecting me.
So from now on.
I will take your place in this battle.
[dark music playing]
[Iksang] The appeasement rite
will begin soon.
It seems the shaman has a strategy.
[dark music continues]
-[King coughs]
-Your Majesty.
Do not make a scene.
[rattling]
-[wind whistling]
-[spectral voice echoing]
[panicked murmuring]
I know the Crown Prince is here.
[spectral voice echoing]
[dark tense music playing]
[music intensifies]
[sizzling]
[music subsides]
So you did become
an ak-gwi after all. brother.
[intriguing music playing]
Do not think of interfering.
All of that bitterness
you must be feeling.
I understand it myself.
A man who was killed by his own father.
it's only natural you'd feel that way.
-[rumbling]
-[Saeng-gang gasps]
-[snarling]
-[gasps]
[Saeng-gang] Brother. stop!
He abandoned me
for hearing the voices of spirits. too.
and my mother died
because of him. brother!
I hate Father as much as you do!
Look at me!
[tense dramatic music playing]
[groans]
[coughing. grunts]
-I told you not to interfere.
-[Saeng-gang gasps]
[music swells]
-[Saeng-gang grunts. gasps]
-[music subsides]
-[Saeng-gang pants]
-[tense music playing]
[tense percussive music playing]
[distant spectral screams]
[squelching]
[Saeng-gang gasps]
[Saeng-gang grunts. groans]
[groans]
-[music intensifies]
-[shaman breathing heavily]
[groans]
[dramatic percussive music playing]
[squelching]
[groans. grunts]
-[music subsides]
-[spectral voice echoes]
[Gu-cheon pants]
[somber music playing]
[breathing shakily]
[strained. labored breathing]
[Gu-cheon groans. grunts]
[breathing shakily]
[King sighs]
-[squelching]
-[Saeng-gang groans]
[Crown Prince sighs]
[Saeng-gang groans]
[Saeng-gang coughs]
[wind whistles]
-[Saeng-gang winces]
-[blade rasps]
[groans]
[pants]
[Saeng-gang groans]
[Saeng-gang groaning]
-[squelching]
-[gasps]
[groans]
[grunts. groans]
[gasps]
[labored breathing]
[Saeng-gang] I will make sure
you don't meet your end tonight.
Even if that means sacrificing
my own life for yours.
[exhales shakily]
[sniffles]
[breathes shakily]
[clatter]
[whimpers]
[whimpers. purrs]
[whimpering continues]
Are you telling me not to do it?
[squeaks]
[Gu-cheon sighs]
This is the only way
I'm able to save the Princess.
[squeaks]
[Gu-cheon] She was willing
to risk her life for me.
so I must answer that resolve.
-[slicing]
-[Gu-cheon groans]
[Gu-cheon gasps]
[Saeng-gang breathing heavily]
[inhales sharply]
[solemn music playing]
[solemn music continues]
[music intensifies]
[King] Humans
advance towards death
from the moment they are born.
No matter what one's status is.
or what kind of person they are.
none of it matters.
At the end of every fate.
death is equal to all.
So there is no reason to grieve
or feel wronged by it.
-[unsettling music playing]
-[distant jingling]
[distant snarling]
[snarling]
[water splashes gently]
[unsettling music continues]
[snarl resonating]
[Gu-cheon] So this is why
the palace reeks of yin energy.
Was all of this you.
Supreme Gwi-mae?
[eerie sound resonates]
I will comply with what you are asking.
In return.
I request the power you hold
so I can save the Princess.
[low growl resonating]
-[unsettling music grows]
-[spectral voices whispering]
[growling resonating]
[spectral voice echoing]
-[groans]
-[spectral screaming]
[chain rattles]
[epic rock music playing]
-[Gu-cheon grunts]
-[howls]
-[spectral screaming]
-[Crown Prince groans]
[squelching]
[spectral screams]
[Crown Prince grunts]
[Gu-cheon grunts]
[grunting]
[both grunt. groan]
[Crown Prince grunts]
[Crown Prince grunts. gasps]
[spectral scream]
[pants]
[spectral screaming]
[spectral voices echoing]
[squelching]
[rumbling]
[epic dramatic music playing]
[spectral growling. screaming]
[Gu-cheon grunts]
[music intensifies]
[both grunting]
[grunts]
[spectral growling]
[music intensifies]
[both grunt]
-[spectral growl]
-[Gu-cheon grunts]
[grunts. groans]
[Gu-cheon grunts]
[music swells dramatically]
-[music subsides]
-How much longer. Your Majesty?
End this! [echoes]
[Gu-cheon grunts]
[King] I. the sovereign. placed you.
the powerless. before the blade
in an attempt to stop the plague.
Without your consent.
I tore apart your fates.
-And yet. I was unable to stop anything.
-[Gu-cheon grunts]
[King] All that reaches me now
are your cries.
filled with rage and grief.
This sin won't be washed away.
It can't.
[Gu-cheon gasps. groans]
[King] These words are not spoken
in the hope of forgiveness.
[pensive music playing]
If you wish to…
you may take my life this very instant.
But if life is still granted to me.
those remaining after your deaths.
the parents.
the siblings.
the children.
every stranded family…
I will care for each one.
[poignant string music playing]
I do this as a promise
for the people of my nation.
[spectral screams]
[King] And as for this sin
that I could not repay in this life.
I will repay again and again
in the afterlife.
So let go of your resentment…
and move on.
[Crown Prince groans. coughs]
[King] Lay down your ties to this world…
and depart now…
for the other side.
[spectral groaning]
[poignant string music continues]
[coughs. pants]
[Gu-cheon sighs]
I waited for the plague spirits to depart.
[chain rattles]
[tense dramatic music playing]
[Gu-cheon grunts]
[music intensifies]
[both grunting]
[straining]
-[Gu-cheon grunts]
-[Crown Prince gasps]
[grunts]
[Crown Prince moans]
[dramatic music playing]
[Crown Prince groans]
[labored] It cannot end like this.
It mustn't.
[groans]
Is your wish
to kill your father so important?
As for me…
I suffered my whole life
constantly believing
that I killed my own mother.
I thought
I would turn into an ak-gwi if I died.
and I forced myself to keep on living
so I wouldn't become what you are.
Why would you go so far
as to become an ak-gwi like this?
[Crown Prince groans]
I wanted to be King.
But none of it matters anymore.
If this palace
will not have me as its King…
Be it that everyone here…
[grunting]
…who live within these walls…
[grunts]
…and those beyond it will all die soon.
[breathes shakily]
I will kill the lot.
[Crown Prince gasping]
All this time. I've tried to avoid
obliterating souls if I could.
[chuckles] You cannot get rid of me.
If you obliterate someone's soul.
then that karma
will make you an ak-gwi as well.
[both grunt]
-[Gu-cheon grunts]
-[Crown Prince gasps]
[blade slices]
I have always known that.
However. the curse won't break.
and the Princess will die
if I don't kill you.
[gasping]
From the moment I met Mother Gwi-mae.
I was ready to become an ak-gwi!
-[Crown Prince gasping]
-[Gu-cheon grunts]
[groaning. gasping]
[music intensifies]
[music subsides]
[stirring ethereal music playing]
It is finally over.
[music subsides]
[flame roars]
[dark ethereal music playing]
[groaning]
[grunts]
[King] Chief Eunuch Kim!
Your…
Gu-cheon!
[spectral screaming]
[chain rattles]
[poignant music playing]
I will give you all the yang energy
I have left to give.
So you can go back.
[spectral scream]
[dark ethereal music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
No. Gu-cheon. wake up. please.
-[melancholy music playing]
-Gu-cheon.
[breathing heavily]
[Saeng-gang] Take my yang energy.
Please take it.
You cannot die like this.
I will not let you go.
Don't die.
Gu-cheon.
I believe that is enough.
[chain rattling]
[distant growl]
Since this is it.
why don't we have some fun?
If my soul is just going to be devoured
by a gwi-mae. then I would rather…
[music fades]
[man] Your Majesty.
There have been no further reports
of plague victims.
The appeasement rites
have all concluded without incident.
and the public sentiment
has already recovered dramatically.
I understand.
You may be dismissed.
[Chief Eunuch] Your Majesty.
All of the strange occurrences
that happened here
have finally disappeared.
[stirring music playing]
[Sukbin] Let us go.
[Chief Eunuch] However.
it is said that the Queen Dowager.
who has withdrawn
to her private residence.
is no longer of sound mind.
[chuckles]
[King] And how is Prince Iksang?
[Chief Eunuch] He is being
discreetly investigated
for summoning shamans
and using them to commit sorcery
to harm you and the royal family.
Your Majesty.
Very well. then.
You may be dismissed.
It has been three days.
[music fades]
Princess.
Should we not give up now
and lay Gu-cheon to rest?
[Ji-yul sobs]
Last time. we thought he was dead as well.
Yet he survived that.
Even if it is Gu-cheon…
Everyone is saying he is dead.
are they not?
[Ji-yul crying]
You can stop crying.
He is not dead.
[crying continues]
[door opens]
[door closes]
See what you've done?
You've even made her cry.
So please stop boiling inside.
and return to yourself at once.
If you cannot find your way back to me.
ring the bell so that I can come
and find you myself.
[breathing shakily]
-[clatter]
-[gasps]
[Ggeomeoksali squeaks]
[pensive music playing]
Ggeomeoksali.
That is a special one.
It's a Ggeomeoksali.
It latches to the living. not a place.
and completely depletes their yang.
The living. not a place.
[gasps]
He is alive.
[breathing heavily]
[Gu-cheon] About 2.000 yards
to the southeast of the temple.
there's a river
that runs along a sheer cliff.
Right near there
is where my mother died.
[breathing heavily]
[Gu-cheon] So even in death.
I cannot leave the temple.
[breathes heavily]
Please…
[breathes shakily]
[music fades]
[bell jingling]
[gasps gently]
-[bell jingles]
-[gasps]
[gasps. sniffles]
I knew you would be here.
[breathing heavily]
It's all in the past now.
You can leave the palace if you'd like.
[voice breaks] You can escape now.
[sobs] So please.
do not stay here alone!
Come back with me.
You once told me you were living
without purpose. unable to die.
Then live.
You can live like a spirit still among us.
Just live!
Are you listening to me at all?
[sobs]
[crying]
[poignant music playing]
Apparently. your life mattered
more than anything. Gu-Cheon.
You told me that!
Did you think
I would be glad about what you did?
That you met your end to save me?
[crying]
You bastard.
Come back this instant. Gu-cheon.
or I'll drag you out!
[sobbing]
[water splashing]
[gasping]
[bells jingling]
[stirring music playing]
[sobs]
[crying]
-[Gu-cheon moans]
-[bell jingles]
[Gu-cheon moaning]
[Gu-cheon] You're crying again.
-[breathing heavily]
-[poignant music playing]
[crying]
[music fades]
[door opens]
So you managed to return to us.
Have you prepared to leave here yet?
Yes. Your Majesty.
However.
it's quite the send-off
you have made for me.
I take it you have no intention
of letting me go easily.
I am aware of a few matters.
Matters that you experienced here
in the palace that you shouldn't have.
You know far too many secrets now.
Secrets about the palace and myself.
Stand up.
[scoffs]
They say one changes entering the outhouse
and when they leave it.
You must know. your word weighs
very little. Your Majesty.
[scoffs]
[uneasy music playing]
Is there something else you can see?
I can see
the souls of the departed King
and of the countless Princes
who will never ascend to be Kings.
[uneasy music continues]
[spectral voices echoing]
You may leave.
Are you freeing me?
[King groans]
Only time will tell.
[door opens]
[door closes]
He won't change his mind and kill me now.
will he? Mm?
[sighs]
[breathes deeply]
[Saeng-gang]
Why are you still standing there?
You can't still be attached to the palace.
[scoffs]
Are you leaving too?
I've decided to come with you.
Huh?
Why would you?
You went out of your way
to help me settle my affairs.
It's my turn now to help you.
Heavens above.
[Gu-cheon sighs]
It will be very hard.
[intriguing music playing]
Don't whine to me later
about how hard it will be for you.
[Saeng-gang] Let us go.
[exciting percussive music playing]
[Gu-cheon scoffs]
[purrs]
[spectral screaming]
[eerie music stinger]
THE EAST PALACE
[exciting percussive music resumes]
[music fades]
[stirring string music playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm